As the chief act for Asia, the work that
myself and also the acties do is very
important to the customers.
>> We have to adapt quickly to evolving
business needs and environments and to
tackle complex problems that require
technical expertise and creative
thinking. On one hand uh we have to
regularly assess the capital position of
the company and to review any potential
risks to us and on the other hand we
have to uh constantly look for
opportunities to optimize the company
and grow the company sustainably.
>> One of the projects that the actual
function has embarked recently is called
actual data modernization to transform
the way we do analysis and to leverage
the the use of AIs further into our
actual analysis
>> as a modeling team. One of the biggest
achievement is that I'm able to share my
opinion on how we do the best practices
for the modeling as well as the
reporting.
>> I would say that working in man life has
enriched my career development a lot
given that it's provided me with a lot
of growth opportunities.
>> Everyone brings in a unique strength and
we complement each other well when we
solve a complex problems.
>> My favorite thing about my team is the
strong collaborative spirit. Everyone is
willing to help and share knowledge.
Many life has given me the opportunity
to rotate across different teams. I
think the flexibility has been a
gamecher for me on a both professional
and a personal level. I have been able
to take on roles that are spread across
different regions including Toronto,
Hong Kong and now Cambodia and Myanmar.
So along the way I think my theaters
have been very supportive to allow me to
move around the roles and regions to
support my career. For anyone who
considering an actural job in manual
life, my advice to them would be to say
yes to every opportunity in manual life.
We value our acties and we provide a lot
of on the job training, job rotation and
succumbs to them. So it's a very good
place for you to grow your career and
also grow yourself professionally and
personally.
>> Now it's a chance to take this
opportunity to explore different actual
functions. The actual career is
definitely evolving and especially in
manual life there's many opportunities
for acties to grow and learn. There's
many areas where acties can contribute
to the success of the company.